<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CrossedPaths</string>
    <string name="concerned">Concerned</string>
    <string name="confirmed">Confirmed</string>
    <string name="clear_history">Clear\n History</string>
    <string name="send_data">Send\n Data</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_6_feet">CrossedPaths @</string>
    <string name="remove_upddates">Remove Updates</string>
    <string name="updates_location">Updates Location</string>
    <string name="check_database">Check\n Database</string>
    <string name="contactUs">Contact\n Us</string>
    <string name="emoji">&#10067;\n</string>
    <string name="login">Enter</string>
    <string name="info">  \nCrossedPaths is an app platform for secure and anonymous location overlap sharing by interested groups.
        If you are interested in setting up your own group, please use envelope icon on the main screen to contact us.\n</string>
    <string name="info_2">CHECK DATABASE shows you the location overlaps you have with other group members in the location and
        time duration setup by your group. It also shows you a short message/explanation from the group\'s administrator. \n</string>
    <string name="info_3">Once you are satisfied with CrossedPaths\'s data privacy and would like to see it adopted to benefit
        private or public affairs, please share with a friend or government official.</string>
    <string name="privacy">Data Privacy Explanation</string>
    <string name="info2">Data privacy is a natural concern for location sharing apps.  CrossedPaths prioritizes data privacy
        employing multiple strategies:\n\n1. All data is stored locally on your phone. No one, not even other apps on your phone,
        can access it. Sharing data with any group administrator is voluntary.  It is your responsibility to read the privacy
        policy of that group which is provided everytime when you send data.\n\n2. You have complete control over when to collect
        data. Data is automatically deleted after a week. You can delete all data at any time.\n\n3. The digital signature of your
        location history instead of your actual location history is stored locally on your phone. These signatures cannot be traced
        back to origin location and time and can only be compared to on another to check if they match.\n\n4. Decentralized model
        lets your phone download the database and compare on the phone. No one else knows your overlap results.\n\n5. Only digital
        signatures of timestamped locations that fit the group adminstrator\'s description are sent to that administrator.  We
        require the administrator clearly specify the specific locations and times that they collect in their privacy policy.
        Through programming, we implement these exact descriptions\n\n6. If you still have reservations on data privacy, a path
        you can take is to start updating location only when you anticipate meeting group members that do not live with you,
        such as going to work or out shopping. At other times, you can turn off the location updates.\n\n7. You are not allowed
        to share your digital signatures collected following one group\'s description to another group, so you will not
        accidentally share data to the wrong group.\n\n8. In rare occasions, we or a third party working with us may ask you
        to voluntarily share all your digital signatures in the past 7 days.  More privacy protocols will be communicated to
        you at that time. A password will be provided to enable you to share those infomration if you choose. \n</string>
    <string name="info2_2">Once satisfied with its data privacy, please share CrossedPaths with friends. If you think such app
        can benefit public affairs in Michigan, please email Governor Whitmer by pressing the icon below.</string>
    <string name="policyTitle">Privacy Policy\n</string>
    <string name="downloadOthers">You selected other... Press to update groups.</string>
    <string name="sendPassword">Warning: You are sending digital tokens of your location history to CrossedPaths.  We discourage this choice and use password protection to prevent accidental sending.  If you insist on sending digital token to CrossedPaths, please contact us first to get the password.</string>
    <string name="groupPassword">Your selected group is passoword protected, please enter correct password to join.</string>
    <string name="policy">\nEffective as of July 18, 2020.\n\n\"Privacy Policy\" describes the privacy practices of CrossedPaths Foundation (\"CrossedPaths,\" \"we,\" \"us,\" or \"our\") in
        connection with the CrossedPaths GPS mobile application (“app”). This Privacy Policy also
        describes the rights and choices available to individuals with respect to their information when using the app.
        \n\nABOUT CROSSEDPATHS\n\nCrossedPaths GPS is an app that provides a platform for users to be voluntarily notified of important information
        based on their location history without sacrificing privacy for the ones who share the information.  For example, a store may want to unintrusively
        promote a product to all people who visited the stores in the recent past.  Another example is person A that visted a restaurant may like to be
        volunteerily contacted by person B who were close at the restaurant at the same time.  Our app provides a platform that may make such desires
        possible.\n\nHOW CROSSEDPATHS WORKS\n\nTimestamped location is always one-way hashed into a string that
        serves as the digital signature of that particular time-space before it is stored. "One-way" means that it\'s nearly impossible to derive
        the original text from the string, thus making it nearly impossible to reverse a digital signature to reveal the original time-space.  However,
        this signature can be used to compare to signuatures in another user\'s phone.  Equal signuatures indicate overlaps of time-space between the
        two devices. A user choose when to track the device\'s location using such digital signatures that become stored on the device for 7 days.
        A copy of these data signatures that fit a group\'s location and time specification that the user wants to be associated with is also saved
        on the device for 7 days.  This copy can be later shared with the group\'s administrator at the user\'s discretion.  Working with us,
        a group administrator can setup a group specifying the time-space range of digital signatures that the group is interested.  Each group provides
        its own privacy policy specifying how they will use the collected data.  Users agreeing with a group\'s privacy policy can voluntarily send
        digital signatures that satisfy the group time-space specification to the group administrator.  After removing all identifiable information,
        the group administrator can publish the shared digital signaturs in an anonymous, aggregated, or de-identified data set where other users
        can download to compare to their digital signatures on their devices.  The only information can be derived for end-user is how many overlaps
        the device had with the data signatures in the data set.  No information about who, where, or how long each overlap lasts can be gained.
        The group administrator can also show a specific message giving context to "overlaps" when an end user choose to download from the group\'s
        data set.\n\nUSER RESPONSIBILITIES\n\nCrossedPaths GPS is designed to facilitate anonymous sharing of digital signatures of location history. As such, it is imperative that you: (i) comply with our terms of use;
        (ii) provide accurate information (including location data) when using the app; and (iii) make informed decisions about how you use
        CrossedPaths including a group\'s own privacy policy before your decision to share any digital signatures with that group\'s
        administrator.\n\nPERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT\n\nInformation you provide to us.\nThe personal information you provide
        to us through CrossedPaths GPS or otherwise may include:\n     •Your email address if you contact us through email, and
        any information you disclose in emails you sent us.\n     •We do not collect digital signatures of time stamped location
        from you.  If you choose to share these digital signatures with a group\'s administrator, please follow that group\'s privacy policy whose link is provided prominently
        above the email button to send data to the group\'s administrator.\n\nHOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION\n\nWe may use your personal information
        for the following purposes and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection:\nTo operate the Service. We may use your personal information to:\n
        •if you share digital signatures with us, the shared digital signatures are merged into an annoymous, aggregated, or de-identified
        data set to publish to other end users.  Once that is done, all personal information including your email address is immediately deleted.\n
        •if you contacted us, we may use your email address to respond to your requests, questions, and feedback.\nTo comply with the law. We may use your personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws,
        lawful requests, and legal processes, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities.\nFor compliance, fraud prevention, and safety. We may use your personal
        information and disclose it to law enforcement, government authorities, and private parties as we believe necessary or appropriate to: (a) protect our, your or others\' rights, privacy,
        safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims); (b) enforce the terms and conditions that govern the app; and (c) protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent,
        harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity.\nTo create anonymous, aggregated, or de-identified data. We may create anonymous, aggregated, or de-identified data from your
        shared digital signatures of location history and other individuals digital signatures. We make personal information into anonymous, aggregated, or de-identified data by removing
        information that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We may use this anonymous, aggregated, or de-identified data and share it with third parties, our Partners, or others for our lawful business purposes.\n
        With your consent. In some cases, we may specifically ask for your consent to collect, use, or share your personal information, such as when required by law.\n\nHOW WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL
        INFORMATION\n\nWe use digital signatures of the location history you share with us to create anonymous, aggregated, or de-identified data. We only share the final anonymous, aggregated, or de-identified data with third parties.
        Other CrossedPaths GPS Users. We will alert users who were within nearby proximity of a sharing user during the preceding 7 days. While this information does not directly identify you,
        there are circumstances when a user could identify you if the user only meets very few people during these days. For example, this may occur if a user met you
        and others that the user can be certain others did not share their digital signatures during the 7 days.\nProfessional advisors. If you contact us other than to
        share digital signatures of your location history, we may disclose your personal information in those contacts to professional advisors,
        such as lawyers, auditors, and insurers, where necessary in the course of the professional services that they render to us.\n
        For compliance, fraud prevention and safety. We may share your personal information for the compliance, fraud prevention and safety purposes
        described above. We will not proactively share your personal information with the government without your consent.\nBusiness transfers.
        We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our business or assets, in connection with a business transaction (or potential business
        transaction) such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy or dissolution.
        \n\nYOUR CHOICES\n\nIn this section, we describe the rights and choices available to all users. Your use of the CrossedPaths GPS is voluntary.
        You can request you shared digital signatures removed by sending those digital signatures again and an instruction to remove as the title. After 7 days, all information is deleted.
        Privacy settings and location data. We make available certain privacy settings on the app, including options to control your sharing of digital
        signatures of your location history. Users of our mobile application also have the choice of whether to allow us to access your precise location data.
        After you allow access, you have the choice when to track your location history and when to stop. You also have the option to delete all the data we
        collected on your phone completely. Your device settings may provide the ability for you to revoke our ability to access location data.
        CrossedPaths GPS will not function as a means for detecting location overlap and information sharing if you do not allow access to your location data.
        Do Not Track. Some Internet browsers may be configured to send "Do Not Track" signals to the online services that you visit. We currently do not respond to "Do Not Track" or similar signals.
        To find out more about "Do Not Track," please visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com.\nChoosing not to share your personal information. Where we are required by law to collect your personal
        information, or where we need your personal information in order to provide the Service to you, if you do not provide this information when requested (or you later ask to delete it), we may not
        be able to provide you with our services. We will tell you what information you must provide to receive our Service by designating it as required at the time of collection or through other
        appropriate means.\n\nOTHER SITES, MOBILE APPLICATION, AND SERVICES\n\nThe apps may contain links to other websites, mobile applications,
        and other online services operated by third parties. These links are not an endorsement of, or representation that we are affiliated with, any third
        party. In addition, our content may be included on web pages or in mobile applications or online services that are not associated with us. We do not
        control third-party websites, mobile applications, or online services, and we are not responsible for their actions. Other websites and services
        follow different rules regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies
        of the other websites and mobile applications and online services you use.\n\nSECURITY PRACTICES\n\nThe security of your personal information is important to us. We employ a number of organizational, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect
        the personal information we collect. However, the security risk is inherent in all internet and information technologies, and we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information.\n
        \n\nINTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS\n\nWe are headquartered in the United States and currently have no service providers in other countries.
        Your personal information remains in the United States.\n\nCHILDREN\n\nAs a general rule, children under the age of 12 years old are not allowed to use the app, and we do not collect personal
        information from them. We encourage parents with concerns to contact us. Children between 12 and 16 years old must have their parent\'s permission to use this app.
        \n\nCHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY\n\nWe
        reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material
        changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating the date of this Privacy Policy and posting it on a new version of the app.\nAny modifications to this Privacy Policy will be
        effective upon our posting the new terms and/or upon implementation of the new changes on the app (or as otherwise indicated at the time of posting). In all cases, your continued use of the
        app after the posting of any modified Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the terms of the modified Privacy Policy.\n\nHOW TO CONTACT US\n\nPlease direct any questions or comments about
        this Policy or privacy practices to havewemetapp@gmail.com.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n</string>
</resources>